# Harold Seo

## WEB DEVELOPER

## **CONTACT**

Los Angeles, CA (213)327-6225 harold.seo.612@gmail.com haroldseo.github.io/portfolio

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### **LANGUAGES**

JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3

## FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES

React, Node.js, Express, jQuery, Mongoose, Bootstrap

## **DATABASES**

MongoDB, PostgreSQL

## OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

Git & GitHub, WordPress, Heroku, EJS, MongoDB Atlas

## **EDUCATION**

#### **GENERAL ASSEMBLY**

Web Development Immersive, 2017

## CSU NORTHRIDGE

Bachelor of Science (BS) Kinesiology and Exercise Science, 2010-2016

## **PROFILE**

Determined and dynamic Web Developer with a passion for delivering functional, responsive, and intuitive solutions. Experience developing multi-faceted projects including a chatting web app, web games, and landing pages. Equipped with a skillset, that incorporates both the knowledge and practice of front-end technologies.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Freelance Web Developer

Aug 2017 - Present

## ChatApp

- Developed a web application using React, where users can chat with other users, in groups, or with a chatbot.
- Implemented socket.io to enable chatting in real-time.

#### TAG

- Developed a web game using JavaScript, where two players compete in a game of tag.
- Implemented jQuery to manipulate the DOM and handle events like collision detection and player movement.
- Wrote game logic to enable smooth gameplay.

## To-Do List

- Developed a checklist using EJS and JavaScript, where users can write and check off daily tasks.
- Incorporated Express to create custom lists by utilizing the route parameters.

## Operations Analyst • NBCUniversal Media, LLC

Aug 2018 - Sep 2019

- Enforced on infringing media content across multiple social media platforms including YouTube Content Management System and Facebook Rights Manager.
- Managed YouTube Content ID queues, claiming and/or releasing videos.
- Collaborated with the engineering team to develop and improve internal operation tools.
- Performed routine audits on asset policies to ensure smooth transitions for domestic monetization and for operational efficiency.
- Actioned on thousands of User Generated Content (UGC) both domestically and internationally for monetization or enforcement.
- Worked closely with the legal team on risk management to mitigate any imminent issues when working with disputed claims.